# MUHAMMAD MAULA FIKRY

Jln S.Parman Bida Ayu Blok D3 No.10, Batam I +62 81268204897 mmaula1312@gmail.com I https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-maula-fikry-b77844175

## **SUMMARY**

As a professional maintainer and expert in PCB design, PLC programming, and 3D design, I have a strong background in electronics and mechatronics engineering, which allows me to develop creative and efficient solutions for a variety of projects. I also have a basis in business knowledge, which I also apply to my competencies. I have also gained in-depth knowledge and have worked in a variety of industries, demonstrating my ability to overcome technical challenges effectively.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Electrical Technician, Global infolink Automation Technology**

April 2022 - August 2022

- Coordinated project tasks to ensure compliance with engineering standards and regulations.
- Conducted thorough project analyses, identifying and rectifying discrepancies in engineering designs.

# Maintenence, Mechatronics Bulding SMK 1

July 2021 - December 2021

- · Coordinating and checking equipment periodically and comprehensively
- Execute projects with client adjustments

## **EDUCATION**

## **Mechatronics Engineering**

July 2018 - June 2022

State Vocational High School 1 Batam

Specializing in automation, electrical wiring and 3D design

# **D3 - Electronic Engineering**

August 2022 - Now

Semarang State Polytechnic

Relevant coursework in eletrical wiring and electronic design.

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Project Management, Electrical installation, Robotics and Automation, CAD
- Certifications: BNSP Cluster Professional Certification Operation and maintenance of
  electronic and electrical equipment, BNSP Cluster Professional Certification Operation and
  maintenance of Pneumatic and Hydraulic equipment, Conventional and CNC Machine Tool
  Operation Cluster, Operation of Programmable Logic Controller (PLC) and Robotic Systems,
  BNSP Certification Industrial Entrepreneurship from Wirausaha Merdeka 2023
- Awards/Activities: 1<sup>st</sup> LKS Mobile Robotics Provinsi Kepulauan Riau, 5<sup>th</sup> Asean Skill Competition Region Industrial Automation, Passed the 2023 PKM PI funding, Passed the 2023 P2MD funding, Passed the 2023 PMW funding